[
  {
    "question": "Secure communication is possible without integrity",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "photoURL": "q5q1"
  },
  {
    "question": "The identity function is collision resistant",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "photoURL": "q5q2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Collision resistance implies second pre-image resistance",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "photoURL": "q5q3"
  },
  {
    "question": "In CBC-MAC, padding the message with \"4\"s to meet the block length is secure",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "photoURL": "q5q4"
  },
  {
    "question": "In CBC-MAC, padding the message with \"1\" followed by \"3\"s until the block length is met is secure.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "True",
    "photoURL": "q5q5"
  },
  {
    "question": "In CBC-MAC, we always need to add a padding block at the end",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "photoURL": "q5q6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does MAC stand for in the context of Cryptography?",
    "answers": [
      "Shorthand for McDonald's",
      "Mandatory Access Control",
      "Media Access Control",
      "Message Authentication Code"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Message Authentication Code",
    "photoURL": "q5q7"
  },
  {
    "question": "To rawCBC είναι επαρκές για να φτιάξουμε secure MACs",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "photoURL": "q5q8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Τα hash functions μπορούν να χρησιμοποιηθούν ως secure MACs",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "False",
    "photoURL": "q5q9"
  },
  {
    "question": "AES is pre-image resistant",
    "answers": [
      "Ναι",
      "Όχι",
      "Ελπίζουμε",
      "Τι είναι το AES? (δεν έχω ξεκινήσει την εργασία #2 ακόμα)"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Ελπίζουμε",
    "photoURL": "q5q10"
  }
]
